Peter, don't forget
you have a physical today at 1:00.
For the hundredth time, Lois,
I won't forget. Nag, nag, nag.
Sometimes I think
I should have married that woman
I met the night of my bachelor party.
Peter, I can't believe
your friends just left you here.
Let's get you home.
Wow, strange lady. You're so sexy.
I should marry you tomorrow
instead of that pain-in-the-ass Lois.
Peter, it's me.
You know what? Screw it.
I am so gonna cheat on Lois right now.
- I don't care if she finds out.
- Peter...
You got a condom? Never mind.
I got this Milky Way wrapper.
- Put this on.
- Why?
Because I'm skipping my physical
to go have steaks with the guys
and I don't want Lois to know about it.
Um.
Okay.
- Lois, I'm going to my physical now.
- Okay, honey. I'll see you later.
Um...
What the hell? I'll just ask it.
Why did we need the horse suit for that?
Okay, all right, that's...
That's seven 16-ounce steaks.
Come on, Joe.
You haven't even finished one.
I mean, that guy had two.
I know, I know, I'm terrible.
Which is why
I'm gonna order the cheesecake.
I can't do it. I'm...
I'm so full.
Full of what? Estrogen.
Come on, take the skirt off, you pansy.
Let's go. Chow down, Mary Jane.
I said, I can't.
- Eat it. Eat the damn steak.
- No.
- Come on! What are you waiting for?
- I can't.
- Eat it, Joe. Eat it!
- No, no, no.
- Joe, eat it!
- I said I'm not hungry!
Where is it now, huh? Where is it now?
Easy, sailor, easy.
Put the gun down, Joe.
Yeah. Nobody's judging you, man.
It's cool.
I'll just put this back in your purse
next to your tampons.
All right, let's start the bidding.
Jennifer, how much do you bid
on the dinette set?
$675, Bob.
$675. Steven?
$780.
- $780. Tammy?
- What was the last bid?
- $780.
- $781.
...you!
Hi, honey. How was your physical?
Good. Good. Good. Yeah. Yeah.
Too good, matter of fact.
You know what the doctor said?
Doctor said I was too healthy, you know?
In too good of shape.
Don't even know how. Too good of shape.
- You didn't go to your physical, did you?
- I did not.
So, Doctor? Is Peter healthy?
My goodness!
You'll be dead within a month.
- What?
Oh, Hдgar the Horrible,
if you keep up that lifestyle
of pillaging and giant turkey legs,
you'll be dead within a month.
Now on to you.
So, what do you think?
Pretty healthy, huh?
Well, Mr. Griffin, let's take a look
at your physical results.
There's a spider in here. Now, here we go.
Mr. Griffin, you're going to
expire in a month.
This is your driver's license, isn't it?
Now, unfortunately,
I'm afraid you are going to die
when you watch
these Dean Martin celebrity roasts.
Will you just tell us how Peter's health is?
Mr. Griffin, I'm not quite sure
how to say this.
Kim Bass-inger, Base-inger,
Basin-jer, Basinger?
- But now on to the cancer.
- Oh, my God!
You are a Cancer, right?
You were born in July?
Now, on to these test results.
My, they're much worse than I thought.
My son got a D minus on his history test.
Now, Mr. Griffin,
that liver's got to come out.
- What?
It's been in the microwave
for three minutes. It'll get dry. Now...
Please. Please.
We can't take any more shtick.
Please, just tell us, is Peter healthy?
Oh, yeah. He's fine. He's just really fat.
- Oh, thank God!
- Wait, wait, wait. Hang on a second.
Did you just say I was fat?
Well, yeah. You are pretty fat.
Um...
Okay. This is news to me.
Boy! This is more awkward
than having sex with a rhinoceros
who doesn't love you anymore.
Why wouldn't you look at me during?
Hey, how was your physical?
Stupid doctor said I was fat.
Can you believe that idiot?
Well, Peter, you are on the large side.
Oh, please, Brian. If I was fat,
could I do this with a Hula-Hoop?
No. No, no, I guess you couldn't do that
if you were fat.
Careful, Peter. That's an old family photo.
My mother gave it to me.
That's weird.
- I didn't know you had a brother.
- I don't.
I mean, I don't think so.
Hey, if I'm fat, then Stewie's fat, too.
Because we wear the same size onesie.
- Hello, pumpkin.
- Hello, Daddy?
Did I miss your piano recital?
No, Daddy. I'm in my 40s now.
Good God!
I had a question I wanted to ask.
Do I have a brother?
No, no. Don't be silly.
'Cause I found this picture...
Oh, Dick. Thank God you're here.
Talk to her.
Message CM-27.
The subscriber you are trying to reach
is unavailable or outside the calling area.
- What do you feel like doing later?
- Message CM-42.
Let's go pay some hookers
to knock our junk around.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Daddy's never gonna tell me the truth.
The only way to find out
is to check the family records.
Breaking into
Grandma and Grandpa's house.
This is more exciting
than that time I saw Bobby McFerrin
fall down all those stairs.
Cool!
Wait. What are you doing?
They're sleeping in here.
Oh, please. They get so doped up
on sleeping pills and liquor,
an earthquake wouldn't wake them up.
My God! How does she sleep at night
knowing she has to funnel
this old duffer's hog?
This is it! Patrick Pewterschmidt.
56 Meadow Lane, Brookfield.
I do have a brother.
Oh, my God. I've got to meet him.
Oh, hey, Brian.
You know what would be fun?
Oh, God, totally!
- Awesome!
You know, sometimes the old-fashioned
playthings are the best.
Hey, kids of America.
It's hand-painted wooden ball in a cup.
Who needs
constant electronic video stimulation
when there's ball in a cup?
Mexico's favorite toy for over 340 years.
Toss the ball, catch it in the cup,
dump it out of the cup, toss it,
and catch it in the cup again.
The ball is on a string
and attached to the cup.
So there's no worry
if you don't catch the ball in the cup.
And cleanup is as easy
as catching a ball in a cup.
So why spend another day
not catching a ball in a cup
when you could be
catching a ball in a cup?
Ball in a cup!
Peter, I think maybe you're in denial
about this fat thing.
Oh, yeah? Well, I challenge you
to prove to me that I'm fat.
Okay, hang on.
- See this?
- Yeah.
- You know what it is?
- Duh, it's an apple.
Good, good, good. All right, watch this.
What the... What is this?
Is this some kind of gag?
- No. That's orbit.
- Huh?
You have your own gravitational pull.
Oh, that's a bunch of crap.
Now back to The Three Stooges.
Can you believe I'm about to meet
my long lost brother?
Maybe Dateline will do a story on us, huh?
I'll get to meet that pompous ass,
Stone Phillips.
He's a kind of guy you hate
till he's inside you.
There it is. 56 Meadow Lane.
"Brookfield Insane Asylum"?
Oh, my God! Mom's brother's crazy.
Oh, no. I didn't catch the ball in the cup.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's okay because the ball is on a string
and attached to the cup.
Doctor, is my brother really insane?
Mrs. Griffin,
we don't use the word "insane. "
We prefer the term "mentally hilarious. "
I can't wait to meet the lunatic.
I bet he's even weirder
than that commercial I saw.
- Hey, is that that new butter substitute?
- It sure is.
Is it true it has half the calories
of butter or margarine
- with all the great taste?
- Yeah.
- Can I have some?
- Get your own.
- Take that, you bitch!
- What the hell?
- How'd you like that?
- Hey, joke's on you. I have hepatitis.
- Patrick?
- Yes?
My name's Lois. I'm your sister.
Oh, my God, Lois.
I never thought I'd see you again.
These are my children.
Why do you live in a crazy house,
Uncle Patrick?
Well, when I was just a little boy,
I had a very traumatic experience.
Mommy, can I have a drink of water?
Jackie Gleason!
Beat it, kid. Your mother's busy.
Pow, right in the kisser!
- That's a horrible story.
- Yes.
I was so traumatized they sent me here.
And I guess
they must have forgotten about me.
Well, you seem perfectly normal to me.
And no brother of mine is gonna be
cooped up in some insane asylum.
We are taking you back to Quahog with us.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Maybe he can bring his sling blade
and order up some
French-fried potatoes.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank God I'm out of that hospital.
It's great to be eating lunch
with my family
instead of a bunch
of chronic masturbators.
Those people are disgusting.
Is it lonely up there
on your pedestal, Patrick?
Oh, Peter, there you are.
This is my brother Patrick.
Yeah, yeah. Good to meet you, Patrick.
All right, listen up, everybody.
I have something to tell you.
I'm not quite sure how to say this.
I'm fat.
Let me give you a minute to absorb that.
That's the way it is.
It's nobody's fault, Meg.
But I've decided to do something about it.
Oh, great.
You gonna drop some weight, fat ass?
No, dummy. I'm gonna help
make this a fat man's world
by establishing the National Association
for the Advancement of Fat People.
This is the best idea I've had
since I slayed that dragon.
- Cybill Shepherd?
- Yes.
People, you are free!
You know, I'm very glad
you're here, Patrick.
Well, I want to tell you that
Marian and I both appreciate
what you've done.
Marian? Oh, you have a girlfriend.
Oh, where are my manners?
Marian is my wife.
She is sitting right next to me.
Oh, here we go.
Oh...
Nice to meet you, Marian.
What's that, honey? Oh, yes. Hang on.
Marian wants some coffee.
Lois, did you see that? He's nuts.
Brian, he's been locked up
in that place for 30 years.
It's perfectly understandable that
he'd invent an imaginary companion.
Yes. He's even more imaginative
than the people who invented singing.
All right, everyone, I'd like to get started.
I'd like to get...
We're start...
You know what? Maybe...
Maybe everyone should sit down.
Okay, that's better.
Welcome, everybody, to the...
Snacks are best saved for later.
Okay, now, I've prepared
an agenda for our organization,
what we want from the community
as fat people with pride.
All right, I think
we got a lot accomplished here today.
We'll pick this up again tomorrow.
Hey, guys, I'm going for a run.
Do me a favor
and keep Marian company while I'm gone.
- Sure.
- Great. Bye, honey.
Hey, Brian.
Marian just called you an alcoholic.
Oh, yeah? Marian just called you a homo.
Wait a second. I'll be right back.
Hey, Brian, Brian.
What if I put this cucumber right here?
Put the cucumber right there.
Do you think Patrick would be angry?
I don't know, man. It's his wife.
You don't think he'd be ticked off
if I put this... Just put that right there?
Just right in that spot,
right there on the couch?
Hey, Marian's giving you a thumb's up.
You know what we should do?
We should let it sit here
for a couple of weeks and see if it pickles.
If after three weeks it pickles,
then she's real
and we both have to buy Patrick a steak.
Hey, pie. I know what you want.
I saw you in that movie.
Whore, slut, bitch.
You don't deserve to have sex with me.
Instead, I'm gonna
eat the whore out of you.
Peter, did you start a coalition
for fat guys?
Yeah. The fat-guy coalition.
Peter, you shouldn't encourage people
to be fat.
- Fat people are immoral.
- How do you figure, sports fan?
They're just bad people,
like that Jackie Gleason.
He was fat and he was bad.
One time when I was a boy...
I love Jackie Gleason.
Hey, take a look at what I bought
at this TV convention.
It's a bus driver's uniform.
Pow, right in the kisser!
- Pow, right in the kisser!
- No!
Wow! That set him off
like a Paul Shaffer fire alarm.
- Hello?
- Lois, it's your father.
The hospital called
and said you released Patrick.
Have you lost your mind?
He's incredibly dangerous.
Oh, well, that's ridiculous.
Patrick is a very nice man.
And you should be ashamed of yourself
for locking up your own son.
Whose pickle is this?
This just in. The body of a local fat man
was found murdered
in Quahog Park last night.
Police released this sketch of the suspect.
Oh, my God!
Police also released this sketch
of a female accomplice
believed to be his wife.
Hello, I'm Tom Tucker.
Quahog's newest serial killer
has struck again.
Since the first victim
at Quahog Park last week,
three more men have been killed,
all of them very, very fat.
- Lois, that sketch looks a lot like Patrick.
- Oh, that's ridiculous.
I don't know. I mean, he's clearly crazy.
Look at that imaginary wife of his.
Well, if she's imaginary, how do you
explain the pickle on the couch?
I don't understand what...
Oh, wait. What? Really?
- Hey, Stewie!
- I know, I know. I heard!
Patrick.
Where have you been?
Oh, it's nothing you need
to concern yourself with, Lois.
Well, that's a relief.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's a relief.
Yeah, the Fat Guy Strangler's living here
and there's a fat guy in the house.
This'll be a bigger disaster than
when Peter did Tara Reid's boob job.
Dropped some pepperoni on there.
You know what? That works. Sew it up.
Michael was one of our brothers.
He was a good man. He was a kind man.
- He was a fat man.
- And now he's a dead man.
And we're all next.
The Fat Guy Strangler's gonna get us.
- He's right.
- Oh, my God.
- We're finished.
- Will someone tie my shoe?
People, people!
I know what will make us feel better.
Let us sing the NAAFP anthem.
All right, everybody,
just make yourselves at home.
Lois, these are the fat guys. Fat guys, Lois.
My God, look at you fat bastards.
I bet none of you can even find
your own penis.
Find your penis for a dollar.
Find your penis, one dollar.
One dollar, find your penis.
Find your penis here.
Peter, what's going on?
Lois, my people are in danger.
Until they find the Fat Guy Strangler,
we will stay...
Victor, don't lean against that.
Hey, everybody.
Peter, you gotta get
these guys out of here.
- Patrick is the murderer.
- What?
You son of a bitch!
Don't listen to Brian.
He doesn't know what he's talking about.
Out of my way, Lois. Your brother is toast.
Warm buttery toast!
- That sounds good.
- I love toast.
- I just found my penis.
- Run, Patrick, run!
After him!
Boys, to your Rascals!
He went into James Woods.
Let's spread out and find him.
We'll head him off at the...
Todd, man, you got to chew your food.
Brian, I know my brother.
He couldn't have done these things.
Well, let's see if you feel that way
when you see this.
Look.
So he has pictures of himself
strangling fat guys.
That doesn't mean
he's the Fat Guy Strangler.
Oh, yeah? What about
the dead fat guy under his bed?
Coincidence?
What about the half-dead fat guy
in the corner?
Patrick tried to kill me.
- Well, maybe it's a different Patrick.
- Lois!
Okay, okay. Oh, my God!
- Peter's out there with him!
- Wait!
You gonna eat that dead fat guy?
How are we gonna find them?
Don't worry, Lois.
I'm good at finding people.
I was the one who found Bush
after Hurricane Katrina.
- Mr. President, are you up there?
- Go away!
- Sir, there's a disaster in New Orleans.
- I'm reading Superfudge.
- You got to come down and deal with this.
- Don't make me do stuff.
Patrick? Patrick!
Crap! Guess we lost him.
Well, nothing left to do
but finish this sentence uninterrupt...
- Patrick, let him go!
- Don't come any closer!
Patrick, let him go or Marian gets it.
Nice try. But Marian's over there.
Don't hurt her!
- Now, let him go!
- Okay! Okay!
- You missed!
- No, I didn't.
That's for rolling up the damn window
when I tried to jump into the General Lee.
I'm sorry, Lois.
I never meant to hurt anybody.
I mean, I did mean to kill those fat guys,
but I never meant to hurt you.
You may be very sick, Patrick,
but I love you.
You're my brother
and you'll always be my brother.
I have to go back to the hospital, don't I?
Yeah. I'm afraid so.
Hey, Patrick. Did you see
how that rock hit me in the face?
It was like, pow, right in the kisser!
Pow, right in the kisser!
Stop screaming, you can't hear me.
I miss Uncle Patrick.
Don't worry, kids.
I promise we can visit him once a month.
We'll be his period.
I was just upstairs and there's
a half-dead fat guy eating a dead fat guy.
So I guess we're just looking
the other way, huh?
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru